knowledgebase.net 2003-06-22

# Knowledge Base Acceptable Use Policy

|  Knowledgebase Solutions, Inc. (KnowledgeBase.net) is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. This statement discloses the privacy practices for KnowledgeBase.net.   
TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build users' trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the  | 

---|---  
use of fair information practices. Because this web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. By displaying the TRUSTe trustmark, this web site has agreed to notify you of:   
  
  * What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identification is collected from you through the web site  

  * The organization collecting the information   

  * How the information is used   

  * With whom the information may be shared   

  * What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information?  

  * The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under (Name of the Company) control   

  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.   

If you have any concerns regarding this statement, you should contact KnowledgeBase.net's privacy administrator by email at privacy@knowledgebase.net. If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact TRUSTe at <http://www.truste.org/users/users_watchdog.html>. TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with the Web site to resolve your concerns.

The purpose of our privacy statement is to make our clients aware of our dedication to preserve KnowledgeBase.net customer privacy. As our services require us to collect client information, KnowledgeBase.net has created this privacy statement in order to communicate our information gathering practices and procedures. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement, and will publish notification on our web site no less than 30 days before the statement modifications take effect. To be effective, the change must first also be approved by TRUSTe, and will include directions on how users may respond to the change. 

**Information Collection and Use**   
KnowledgeBase Solutions Inc, located at 5657 Wilshire Blvd Suite 410, Los Angeles, CA 90036, Tel: 323-857-5787, email: privacy@knowledgebase.net, and LivePerson NASDAQ(LPSN), 462 Seventh Avenue - 21st Floor, New York, NY 10018 , Phone: 212.609.4200, email: questions@liveperson.com, [LivePerson Privacy Policy](http://www.liveperson.com/help/privacy.asp) are the organizations collecting the Personally Identifiable Information and/or Third Party Personally Identifiable Information through the Site. 

When a user contracts KnowledgeBase.net services, the user is required to provide such information as their name, company name, address, phone number, e-mail address, product selection, and billing information. It is possible that we will also ask for additional information such as company industry, number of employees, etc., at the time our service is contracted or if interest in our services is expressed. It is optional for customers to provide this additional information, and users may choose not to do so when they activate services with KnowledgeBase.net or request information on our services. 

When KnowledgeBase.net captures user information upon sign-up, we use the client information to activate the customer account. Once a client has signed up with KnowledgeBase.net, future mailing may periodically be sent out to the KnowledgeBase.net client base, introducing new products, product updates, and important KnowledgeBase.net news and information. Our users and clients have the option of receiving the KnowledgeBase.net company newsletter. Should a client choose to receive the newsletter via e-mail, we will not distribute the user e-mail address for any other purpose than the sending of our newsletter or other KnowledgeBase.net service information. If a user would like to cease receiving the newsletter or other promotional e-mail correspondence from KnowledgeBase.net, they may send an e-mail request to support@knowledgebase.net and immediately be removed from future mailings. KnowledgeBase.net requires a valid, working e-mail address upon account setup in order to send our client account information details, including a welcome packet, and account username and password. 

KnowledgeBase.net does not disclose any user/customer information to any third party, other than what we explicitly state upon account activation or as detailed in our Terms of Use. Billing and financial information is required upon account activation for KnowledgeBase.net to bill for services rendered. KnowledgeBase.net will only use this billing information to verify the validity of the account, and bill for KnowledgeBase.net services. When KnowledgeBase.net bills for services rendered, a third-party processing company is used to charge customer credit cards and collect payment. This third-party is used only to process credit card charges, and does not store or distribute customer credit card or billing information. 

Additionally, the KnowledgeBase.net website may contain content from third-party content providers, but these content providers neither receive nor distribute KnowledgeBase.net user or customer information, nor do they receive user or customer information from KnowledgeBase.net. 

Knowledgebase.net provides a service where our customers upload and store their data on KnowledgeBase.net servers and equipment. KnowledgeBase.net does not review, edit, disseminate, or use this data in any way, except as may be required by law, or as outlined in our Terms of Use. Customer data or records may be viewed from time to time to handle a technical support request that is initiated by the client, or to resolve any other problem or technical issue. Additionally, individual records may be viewed if required so by law, or if there is a suspected Terms of Use violation. 

KnowledgeBase.net users are solely and individually responsible for maintaining the privacy and confidentiality of their own data, as well as their usernames and passwords. KnowledgeBase.net may collect information from visitors to the KnowlegeBase.net web site. Most commonly, we may collect the Internet addresses of KnowlegeBase.net site visitors. We use the information that we log from the KnowledgeBase.net website to both improve our services, and help troubleshoot possible KnowledgeBase.net website problems. We may also analyze non-identifying statistics that we collect from website visitor usage, and provide this data to qualified third parties. 

**Cookies**   
Security protocols put into operation by KnowledgeBase.net are determined by encrypted session Ids and dynamic data. Should you select to activate the KnowledgeBase.net "Remember Me" feature, we will use a "cookie" that contains partial or full authentication information depending on your preference. The cookie will reside on your local system. Further, We use a third party to provide statistical analysis regarding our users use of the www.knowledgebase.net web site and may set cookies in order to gather the information needed to perform their statistical analysis. The information collected by the third party cookies does not contain any personal information or can be linked back to any individual user. 

**Log Files**   
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Links**   
Our web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we Knowledgebase Solutions, Inc. are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site or the KnowledgeBase.net application. 

**Surveys**   
From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information and demographic information. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site or of the Knowledgebase.net application. 

**Security**   
KnowledgeBase.net has chosen to implement the latest technology that allows for the highest levels of Internet security that are possible today. If you are accessing our site with 4.0 versions or higher of Microsoft Internet Explorer or Netscape Navigator browsers, your information is encrypted and authenticated, using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. The SSL systems provide complete data security for you and your users, and the authentication ensures that your valuable content is available only to registered users, and is not accessible to unwanted parties. Each registered user in your organization is provided with a unique username and password. Each time a user logs onto your KnowledgeBase.net application, they can only be authenticated and allowed access using the correct username and password that has been assigned. A session is issued for the purpose of capturing encrypted authentication data for the length of the session. Neither the username nor the password is included in the session. Security protocols put into operation by KnowledgeBase.net are determined by encrypted session Ids and dynamic data. Should you select to activate the KnowledgeBase.net "Remember Me" feature, we will use a "cookie" that contains partial or full authentication information depending on your preference. The cookie will reside on your local system. 

**Opt-Out Policy**   
KnowledgeBase.net offers its visitors and customers a means to choose how we may use information provided. If, at any time after registering for information or ordering Services, you change your mind about receiving information from us, send us a request specifying your new choice. Simply send your request to support@knowledgebase.net. 

LivePerson Privacy Policy: KnowledgeBase uses LivePerson to provide our customers with the ability to use chat as a means of communication with our employees. LivePerson Privacy policy is as follows: 

**LivePerson Users**

**What information do we collect from LivePerson Users?**   
When the online customer service chat first begins, LivePerson Users are asked to enter their names in whatever format or detail they prefer. During the chat, LivePerson Users enter into a live question and answer session with an operator. We maintain dialogue transcripts of these chats. After the chat, we ask LivePerson Users to fill out an exit survey in order to obtain valuable feedback about our service. Filling out the exit survey is completely voluntary. The surveys may ask for contact information (e.g., email address) and for demographic information (e.g., zip code, age or income level). 

LivePerson Users in need of technical support are required to complete a form for purposes of defining and clarifying their technical support requests. When submitting a technical support request, LivePerson Users are asked to provide the following identifiable information: email address, URL of their site and a description of the issue. Emails sent to support are kept only for problem solving purposes and this information is not shared with or disclosed to any outside third parties. 

We log browser information (e.g., Internet Protocol addresses and browser types) to help diagnose problems with our server, gather broad demographic information and administer our site. 

We also collect data through aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our site. 

We do not knowingly collect any information from anyone under 18 years of age. The exit surveys ask LivePerson Users to enter their age so that we may refuse to accept any information that has been submitted by anyone under 18. 

How does LivePerson use information it collects from LivePerson Users and will LivePerson disclose such information to outside parties? 

We access the information we collect for certain purposes (for example, to aggregate the information, to monitor the use of the service during certain chats and for other lawful purposes). A LivePerson User’s information, including personally identifiable information, will not be shared with anyone. We do not sell, trade or rent the personal information that LivePerson Users provide. 

**LivePerson ASP Users**

_What information do we collect from ASP Users?_   
When the online customer service chat first begins, ASP Users are asked to enter their names in whatever format or detail they prefer. During the chat, ASP Users enter into a live question and answer session with an operator. We maintain dialogue transcripts of these chats. After the chat, our customers may ask ASP Users to fill out an exit survey in order to obtain valuable feedback. Filling out the exit survey is completely voluntary. The surveys may ask for contact information (e.g., email address) and for demographic information (e.g., zip code, age or income level). The surveys vary by customer so that our customers may obtain feedback specific to their website and business, as well as feedback regarding our service. 

We log browser information (e.g., Internet Protocol addresses and browser types) to help diagnose problems with our server, gather broad demographic information and administer our site. 

We do not knowingly collect any information from anyone under 18 years of age. The exit surveys ask ASP Users to enter their age so that our clients may refuse to accept any information that has been submitted by anyone under 18. 

_How does LivePerson use information it collects from ASP Users and will LivePerson disclose such information to outside parties?_

We access the information we collect for certain purposes including, but not limited to, the following: to provide maintenance, support or professional services to our customers, to aggregate the information, to monitor the use of the service during certain chats and for other lawful purposes. 

An ASP User's information contained in the dialogue transcripts and the exit surveys may be shared with our customer on whose website the ASP User accessed our service (the "ASP Customer"). Furthermore, such information may be shared with others on an aggregate basis. Personally identifiable information or business information related to an ASP Customer or ASP User (supplied voluntarily during the chat or in the exit survey) will not be shared with parties other than the ASP Customer, except as required by law. We actively encourage the ASP Customers to post a privacy policy on their site and to ensure that their use of the information will comply with their privacy policy. 

We do not sell, trade or rent the personally identifiable information that ASP Users provide. 

_Information Relevant to Both LivePerson Users and ASP Users_

_How does LivePerson protect user information?_   
Our site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We offer secure sessions for chats at our clients’ option so that data passed between users and operators cannot be decrypted. To achieve this level of security, we use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption that encodes information as it is being sent over the Internet between the user and the operator. All chats and user data are maintained and archived on secure servers. Access to stored data is password protected and passwords are account specific. Therefore, no customer can view data for another customer. We also use appropriate firewall technology within our facility to prevent unauthorized access. For another level of protection, all data is backed up daily, and archives are stored off-site in a secure location. 

_What about "cookies"?_   
Cookies are pieces of information that some websites transfer to the computer that is browsing that website and are used for record-keeping purposes at many websites. Use of cookies makes Web-surfing easier by performing certain functions such as saving passwords, lists of potential purchases, personal preferences regarding the use of the particular website and to make sure the user does not see the same ad repeatedly. Many consider the use of cookies to be an industry standard. Our site uses cookies to enhance the user's experience by allowing us to recognize a user's return visit to our own service. 

Browsers are usually set to accept cookies. However, if users would prefer not to receive cookies, they may alter the configuration of their browser to refuse cookies. If they choose to have their browser refuse cookies, it is possible that some areas of our site will not function as effectively when viewed by the users. 

Opt-Out Policy   
LivePerson gives users options wherever necessary and practical. Such choices include opting not to engage in chat sessions and opting not to provide identifiable information during chat sessions. 

**Correcting and Updating Your Information**   
To update billing information or discontinue the Service please email support@knowledgebase.net or call 323-857-1250. 

**Additional Information**   
If you have any questions about this Statement or the practices of our website, you can send an email to privacy@knowledgebase.net.
